Lily Liu

07308686787, lilycliu@outlook.com, https://portfolio-lilyclius-projects.vercel.app/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/lily-liu-323568b2/, https://github.com/LilycLiu, New Malden, London

Personal Profile

Junior Web Developer holding Master's Degree in Art Museum & Gallery Studies with 10 years working experience. I learnt front-end skills from bootcamp and self-teaching. I enjoy building responsive websites and playing with database.

Technical Skills

- Typescript
- React
- Tailwind CSS
- Sass
- Javascript
- MongoDB
- Git
- HTML5
- CSS
- Next.js

Education & Qualifications

Openclassroom, UK

July 2023 – Oct 2023

Web development online bootcamp

University of Leicester, UK

Oct 2011 – Sept 2012

• MA Art Museum & Gallery Studies

National Chiao Tung University, Taiwan

Sept 2004 – June 2008

• Bachelor Degree in Art Humanities and Social Science

Work Experience

FACT https://www.fact-uk.org.uk/

Due Diligence Researcher/Data Processor at a research company in London. *May* 2020 – *May* 2023 Duties included:

- To conduct open source research and collection of intended subject matter according to business needs: political, security, socio-economic, and terrorism issues
- Process visa/citizenship applications and to consolidate foreign language information into
 English, and produce clear and concise written research reports

Jan De Nul Group https://www.jandenul.com/en

Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

Office Manager at a construction & renewable energy company in Taiwan.

Duties included:

- Assist the director with the management of his workload; prioritising accordingly.
- Filing, Scanning, Photocopying, Organising the meeting room calendar and Set up.
- International and national travel arrangement, Orgnising company events.
- Ordering office supplies, Contacting suppliers and Processing PO/Invoice.
- Supporting cash expense, HR hiring process and Dealing with shipping documents.

Bahamas Maritime Authority https://www.bahamasmaritime.com/ Apr 2015 – Nov 2018

Administrative Assistant at the Bahamas government organization in London.

Duties included:

- Answering incoming calls and emails via customers.
- Account manager for multiple clients.
- Issuing seaman's books and endorsements for seafarers.

July 2014 – Mar 2015

Sales Administrator at an e-commerce furniture company in London.

Duties included:

- Providing excellent customer support in a timely manner and Sales order processing.
- Stock control and Creating sales documents chasing up vendors.
- Administration of key customer accounts and supporting HR duties.
- Maintaining pricing information on ERP system and annual distribution of sales prices.
- Keeping up to date with all new process that require sales support input.

Egistec Inc Feb 2013 – June 2014

Logistics and Purchasing Administrator/Customer Service at a technology company in Taiwan.

Duties included:

- Stock control and Handling shipping documents and forwarder arrangement.
- Issuing Purchase Orders with relevant information (supplier, factory, sales)
- Engaging & replying to customer correspondence (emails, and phone calls).
- Preparing invoice and payment requests with correct sign off to Finance.

References

References will be made available upon request.